{
    "id": "57579735449d4163bf151358f855e34e",
    "title": "Subject Verb Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My brother and I …………….. cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "52bdf668a5a14907bea30e65e84f8825"
        },
        {
            "question": "The quality of the apples ………………. not very good.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc81b4a0c3234b90be049927a975943b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rise and fall of the tide ………………. due to the attraction of the moon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96e94022ef1e48c0b3b5e081db65c4d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The state of his affairs ………………. such as to cause anxiety to his creditors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce8f7203c6014bada122ad9c2e081839"
        },
        {
            "question": "He or his friend …………… the secret.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knows"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98da31d15da141f1a1d93e4393eb038f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Time and tide ……………….. for none.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "waits"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6adbd8a3fb27408182529b7320805a1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither he nor his friend ……………… there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ddeee08a49f4b5b8b7d80b17d478e0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Either he is mistaken or I ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "am"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "802c2b2b85714394bfbbbc9a1e15e929"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wool, as well as cotton, ………………. exported from India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b911cbffdd8407cbd238a6aef50c81b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The leader, as well as his followers, …………….. excited.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc38547f7d1a4613b96ab73686a54074"
        }
    ]
}